const questions = {
  questions:[
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'a',
      font: 'kulitan',
      options: ['A', 'E', 'Ba', 'Da'],
      correctAnswer: 'A',
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'aa',
      options: ['Ka', 'Da', 'á-â', 'í-î' ],
      correctAnswer: 'á-â',
  },
{
id: 3,
question: 'ba',
options: ['Na', 'Ni', 'Ba', 'Ta' ],
correctAnswer: 'Ba',
},
{
id: 4,
question: 'Da',
options: ['Ka', 'Mi', 'Sang', 'Da' ],
correctAnswer: 'Da',
},
{
id: 5,
question: 'E',
options: ['U', 'Gi', 'E', 'Lu' ],
correctAnswer: 'E',
},
{
id: 6,
question: 'Ga',
options: ['Gu', 'Ge', 'Sa', 'Ga' ],
correctAnswer: 'Ga',
},
{
id: 7,
question: 'i',
options: ['Bang', 'Nga', 'i', 'í-î' ],
correctAnswer: 'i',
},
{
id: 8,
question: 'ii',
options: ['a', 'Ba', 'i', 'í-î' ],
correctAnswer: 'í-î',
},
{
id: 9,
question: 'ka',
options: ['Ka', 'Ba', 'Ke', 'Ki' ],
correctAnswer: 'Ka',
},
{
id: 10,
question: 'la',
options: ['Ku', 'La', 'Ma', 'Mi' ],
correctAnswer: 'La',
},
{
id: 11,
question: 'ma',
options: ['Mo', 'Lu', 'Ma', 'Mi' ],
correctAnswer: 'Ma',
},
{
id: 12,
question: 'Na',
options: ['Ya', 'Wa', 'Ne', 'Na' ],
correctAnswer: 'Na',
},
{
id: 13,
question: 'Nga',
options: ['Ngo', 'Nga', 'Li', 'Yu' ],
correctAnswer: 'Nga',
},
{
id: 14,
question: 'o',
options: ['a', 'e', 'i', 'o' ],
correctAnswer: 'o',
},
{
id: 15,
question: 'pa',
options: ['Ta', 'Ba', 'Ka', 'Pa' ],
correctAnswer: 'Pa',
},
{
id: 16,
question: 'Sa',
options: ['Sa', 'Ga', 'Pa', 'La' ],
correctAnswer: 'Sa',
},
{
id: 17,
question: 'ta',
options: ['Nga', 'Ngi', 'Ta', 'Ti' ],
correctAnswer: 'Ta',
},
{
id: 18,
question: 'u',
options: ['ú-û', 'u', 'a', 'e' ],
correctAnswer: 'u',
},
{
id: 19,
question: 'uu',
options: ['ú-û', 'u', 'a', 'e' ],
correctAnswer: 'ú-û',
},
]
};

export default questions;

  